Nathan Holland

Animator - Levitate Media

Salt Lake City, UT - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Nathan-Holland/5547704ea4dc2fbe

My name is Nathan Holland and I've been animating motion graphics and infographic animations for over 4 years now. I enjoy working with a variety of subjects and in a variety of styles, (utilizing Adobe After Effects and Toon Boom Harmony primarily) so I can work with whatever vision you've got. The most important thing to me is that you are satisfied with the finished project.

Please take a look at a short demo reel of some of my work here: https://youtu.be/t9DAQ4vFoyY Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Animator

Levitate Media - September 2016 to Present

I work with clients to create infographic animations for their businesses. I design the storyboards off of provided scripts and design the imagery to best cater to the client's wishes.

Animator

Twig Media - December 2014 to Present

I have collaborated on various projects to craft hand-drawn digital animation clips using provided voiceovers.

Sustain3 - Animator

- May 2014 to Present

The client gave me freedom to script, storyboard, and animate informational animations in a variety of styles. I have been given enough creative freedom to use each project as an opportunity to learn new techniques.

Animator

University of Utah - November 2015 to August 2016

The Got Entrepreneurship team met every week, and we crafted storyboards to animate informational anecdotes off of.

Teacher's Aide

University of Utah - January 2015 to May 2015

I had the privilege to aide professor Lien Fan Shen in teaching the Intro to Animation class. Students were free to come to me for assistance and critique as they made their first forays into the world of animation.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Fine Arts in Film and Media Arts in Course highlights

Univeristy of Utah August 2012 to May 2016

SKILLS

After Effects (Less than 1 year), AUTODESK MAYA (Less than 1 year), Flash (Less than 1 year), ILLUSTRATION (Less than 1 year), Illustrator (Less than 1 year)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

Over the course of my various jobs, I've acquired skills using Flash, Maya, Toonboom Harmony, After Effects, Photoshop, Illustrator